This is how I'll become.
Supreme Commander!
A hero!
This is my story!
In the darkness of the dark?
One, one, another one!
The tears of tears.
The dream of the dream?
Oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh.
I'll continue to join you.
I have nothing to fight.
We'll do it once again.
Every time that leads you to this cloud?
I'll never forget how it's gonna be.
Oh my God !
I'll never forget how it's going.
We are all the way up!
Perfect!
Squeaky clean!
A job well done truly is its own reward.
Too bad about this location.
It's not exactly pleasant.
The barrier!
I guess the Shuki can show
up close to the dorm, too.
Mr.
Yuki, are you okay?
Huh?
Oh, hi, Nei. Welcome home.
The seventh squad is in
Mato's unlucky Urakimon area.
That's the reason why more Shuki
appear here than the other dorms.
Urakimon?
Mato is an alternate dimension
that's as big as the city of Tokyo!
It's pretty cool!
It's divided up into
eight different sections,
and each section has its own
demon defense force station there.
We skip over force since it's a bad omen.
I see.
You're a lifesaver, thank you.
I have so much to learn.
I'm still clueless when it comes to Mato.
It's Snee's job to teach you things.
You're welcome!
I'm not sure I'll ever get used to
a child having seniority over me.
By the way, do we need to
do something about that?
Don't worry about that one.
That's just a small fry.
We can safely ignore it.
Well...
Hey!
Chit-chatting instead
of working, Yuki Wakata?
That was so reckless!
What if you'd hit us?
Don't underestimate my skills.
If I wanted to you'd have a
bullet in your skull. Oh, come on.
You're missing the point entirely
Why don't you run along
and get dinner ready?
Yeah, yeah, do I sense an attitude?
You should be grateful.
The only reason a man like you has
the privilege of living in our dorm
Being a caretaker sucks.
Let's go
Is someone there?
Probably nothing.
I'm so impressed, Yuki!
You really are a talented chef!
I'm not a picky eater, but I am
glad we're getting nutritious meals.
Well, I'll have seconds, I suppose.
Do you think you can
teach Jay how to cook?
Keep up the good work when you
do the dishes and clean the tub.
Same goes for cleaning the
spare rooms in the watchtower.
Got it.
Wait a second.
I wanted to be a hero.
Now I'm just a freaking maid.
Um, Miss Kyouka, when we first met, we
discussed me assisting you out in the field.
But I feel like chore work
is all I ever do around here.
I will use you in the
field when you're needed.
Until that time, you're free to
concentrate on your housekeeping tasks.
Please!
I know you can't possibly be stupid enough
to complain about the commander's orders.
Her arm turns into a sword!
This is an all-girls dorm.
I have no doubt that some of you are
uncomfortable with the male caretaker.
But he's a skilled housekeeper,
and he's essential for my ability.
So please, try to treat him kindly.
If he misbehaves or screws up in any way,
I will do my duty as his
master and twist it off.
Is that acceptable, right?
Twist what off?
Nay!
I'm gonna hop in the back!
Aaaaaaah!
Hm.
Uh... Huh?
Oh, God!
That scared me!
You were peeking! Uh...
I could have sworn I heard Shushu's voice.
I'm up here! Huh? Huh?
Naughty!
You finally let your true
colors show! Shushu? Oh, God!
Did I surprise you?
Uh...
My ability allows me to grow and shrink.
Hmm.
What the...
Hey, what was that?
I've been keeping a close eye on you, Mr.
Caretaker.
I wanted to know what makes a man tick.
Lucky, lucky!
Picture perfect, am I right?
Ah! Delete it! Delete it now!
I wonder what the commander's
gonna think about this.
Think she'll twist it off?
Uh, are you threatening me?
What do you want?
You want money?
I just like to keep things interesting.
So if you don't want me to leak this,
then you'll have to become my slave, Mr.
Caretaker. What the?
I already am a slave!
Huh.
Romance manga just doesn't do it for me.
The action-adventure stuff
gets me way more amped up.
Don't you agree, Mr. Caretaker?
Sure.
Yeah, I figured as much.
If I don't delete that photo on her phone,
she's going to blackmail
me for the rest of my life.
I'm bored.
Now's my chance.
You're such a naughty little
slave, holding something like that.
Oh, you're as red as a tomato.
Are you feeling tense?
Hey, you did that on purpose.
Oh, you silly boy.
So predictable.
Okay, but are you really okay with
me handling your unmentionables,
even though I'm a guy?
I'd be creeped out if you did
something weird with them.
But I suppose I don't really
think of you as a guy.
If anything, you're more like
a neat little pet. A pet?
And besides, you're our
obedient housekeeper.
And that's just another piece
of clothing for you to tidy up.
So you're free to touch them all you like.
Right, then I'll organize.
I can use that as blackmail material too!
Quit taking photos of me!
Still, the whole photo thing
was a misunderstanding.
Even if she rats me out to Kyoka,
I could explain my side of it.
What's happening?
You have to move faster, Himari!
Don't give the enemy a chance to attack!
Right!
The impact will be strong
enough to slay a Shuki,
but it's an easy way to
throw them off balance!
Be a fan!
You must be swift, brutal, and sharp! Ah!
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
Ah! Ah!
Ah!
Watch me!
And that's how you perform a combo!
Oh, without using your ability!
You're amazing, Commander!
You managed to kill!
I'm so screwed!
I can't risk giving Kyoka
the wrong impression!
Uh, oh, hi, Nei.
I have news for you as your senpai.
Sure, I'm listening.
The commander Himari and Nei will be
leaving the dorm to attend a meeting,
so keep an eye on things
with Shushu while we're gone.
Alone with Shushu?
Miss Shushu is a really nice person,
so I think it'll be a good opportunity
for you to get to know her better.
That is not the face of a nice person.
Fantastic perfect for soothing my muscles
after an intense training session.
Why am I letting her walk all over me?
Enough's enough I gotta put
my foot down once and for all!
Or I could keep it up for
a little longer I guess
Hey how'd you get so
good at giving massages?
Well, I used to give them to my
big sister, so I had practice.
So you've got a big sister just like me.
You have siblings?
I have two older sisters.
I'm the youngest.
I grew up without a dad, and I've
only attended all-girls schools,
so I've never talked to a guy before you.
So that's why you
thought I was so strange.
I was watching your every move.
And then I decided to turn you into my
slave, because it seemed like so much fun!
Do you realize how crazy that sounds?
Maybe it does, but in my opinion, having
fun in life is the most important thing.
It's why I moved to Mato.
I was looking for excitement.
That's your reason?
Even though you could die? Sure!
Slaying Shuki is a total blast!
It's like I'm the protagonist
of an adventure manga!
I feel so much better!
Hey, let's play a fighting game!
Okay, but you should know I'm
pretty good at video games.
Then why don't we spice things up?
The loser has to strip off a piece
of their clothing what hold on?
Obviously slaves don't have the
right to refuse their master.
Fine by me bring it I'll beat her
and then force her to apologize!
K .O.
K .O. K .O.
You win.
You're way too easy to take down.
But my friends won't
even let me play as Guile
because I always end
up kicking their asses.
Come on, time to get naked.
But wait, taking off my
underwear would be a crime.
We're here in Mato.
It's not that big a deal.
Go ahead, take him off.
I gotta say, I've never
seen a guy exposed,
so I'm kind of curious to
see what it looks like.
But wait, you have to
remember that I'm a man.
What if I start feeling frisky?
It's not safe for you, Shushu.
You could get hurt.
Oh, what's not safe?
You ought to trust your gut
whenever there's danger involved.
Huh?
That's what you were worried about?
How adorable!
I'll be just fine.
I would never let a man
take advantage of me.
I forgot about her ability.
You're the one in danger here.
Hey!
Wait a second, Shushu!
No can do!
Now that you're incapacitated,
it's time to accept your punishment?
and show me what you're hiding underneath.
Shushu!
Your hands are cold!
It's so teeny-weeny and adorable!
That's hilarious!
An attack!
And Kyoka and the others are still gone!
The barrier!
You can wait here.
I've got this. Uh, hey!
Guys are too wimpy.
Be a good boy and stay put.
Overpowering us with your size?
Not a bad strategy.
Unfortunately, I've got the upper hand.
Taste my Peach ability!
Paradigm Shaft!
She's huge!
Is that all you've got?
Uh-huh!
Uh-huh.
Hi!
Follow-by, another kick!
Whoa.
Turning into a giant
sure is exhausting work.
Shushu, behind you! Huh?
So there was another one hiding nearby.
Sneaky.
Always keeping me on my toes!
If I don't finish this quick,
things could get hairy.
Paradigm shift!
Huh?
What the?
Oh, crap!
Shushu!
It looks like she's in real trouble.
I want to transform, but without
Miss Kyoka, it's impossible.
There must be something I can do to help.
I transformed when my tongue
touched Miss Kyoka's hand.
So by that logic...
I got it!
If I lick something that belongs to
her, I should be able to transform.
I didn't transform, but
I'm on the right track.
I need something that
provokes a stronger reaction.
Please forgive me.
It worked for a second.
If her shirt does a better job...
Oh God, what does this
say about me as a person?
This is my life now!
There's no time to be indecisive.
If I want to be a hero, I
have to act like a hero.
And if licking her boot makes
my dream come true, I'm in!
Maybe I got carried away, whipping
out the jumbo size like that.
A bad habit of mine.
I'm probably going to shrink back soon.
You only transformed halfway
through? That's a first!
But still, I gotta try!
Hold it still!
Come here!
I... did it!
Too late.
I'm out of time.
My body...
won't move.
Hold on! This is it!
No way!
You saved my life, but...
I can't! I'm stuck!
Forcing a transformation?
That's a little over the top.
I did it cuz you said guys are too wimpy.
Be good and stay put.
I wanted to prove that you were wrong
Oh my god!
Hm? No!
I was naked when I transformed!
This isn't what it looks like, okay?
He gets excited whenever
I transform! Calm down!
This isn't the time!
Please, I'm begging you, go down!
Go down!
It's kind of impressive, actually.
Oh, please, Ms.
Kyoka, be gentle with me!
Just lie still!
Out of commission after
a few minutes in combat?
How pathetic.
Oh, shut up!
Listen, shouldn't we fix the cracks in
the barrier that are all around the dorm?
No need to worry.
The barriers protecting
important locations such as our
dormitory and the peach groves
have special properties.
So long as the damage is
minor, it will repair itself.
Oh, it was the same then, too.
But more importantly, quit worming!
This is the reward I get for
forcing myself to transform!
No more slaying Shuki for
kicks, got it, Shushu?
Underestimating your opponent
is how you end up in a body bag.
Yes, ma 'am.
I should have known better.
You can thank Yuki by assisting
him with his household duties.
Right.
Hey, what the hell are you doing?
I'm asserting dominance as your master.
Now you've got me even more
curious about guys than before.
So let's keep our arrangement.
How the hell did you
get the perfect photo?
Well, till next time, Mr. Caretaker.
Wait, don't go yet.
She's got too many
incriminating photos of me.
I can't talk my way out.
Will I ever be free of this torture?
I won't give you up, Yuki.
Go on without me!
Inform the commander ASAP! Roger that!
That's no ordinary Shuuki.
Yuna! Karu!
Do not eat her.
I knew I felt it.
I'm positive.
I can feel his presence anywhere.
Yuki is somewhere in Mato.
I'd better pay him a visit.
Oh
Thank
you
so
much for watching.
One, two, two,
two slowly By going up again Chou
cha bs I'll take the power of my power
If I want two, I'll take it
If I want you to take it I'll take it easy
I'll take it easy I'll take it easy
I'll take it easy to
continue I'll leave you
I'll take it easy
Okay, let's talk about Ms.
Shushu's Peach Ability Paradigm Shift.
With that, she can alter the
size of her body at well.
But not just that.
She can also alter the size of her clothes
or even simple objects simultaneously.
Comes in handy when moving to a new house.
By the way, the dorm has
its own Wi-Fi network.
Ms.
Shushu spends a lot of time
playing online multiplayer games.
She lets Snake join in, too!
Anyway, next time,
encounter Kyouka Rampage.